# Name: Tammineedi J S R Vyjayanthi

SAP Security/GRC Consultant

Mobile: 8978976703

Email: tvyjayanthi@gmail.com

#### **Professional Profile**

I am an enthusiastic and **professional SAP Security and GRC Consultant with 3 years of experience** who enjoys being part of a successful and productive team. I am quick to grasp new ideas and concepts, and to develop innovative and creative solutions to problems. I can work well on my own initiative and along with the team to meet the tightest of deadlines. Even under significant pressure, I possess a strong ability to perform effectively.

### **Professional Summary**

Having 3 years of experience as a SAP Security & GRC Consultant in a professional environment which includes:

- End to end user support to fix user's problem.
- Coordinate with different functional teams to design roles successfully.
- Experience with the following SAP Products
  - **♣** ECC 6.0
  - **♣** GRC Access Control 12.0
- Performed User Administration including creating users, creating roles, assigning profiles, assigning roles.
- Assigning authorization objects to roles using profile generator.
- As security consultant, experience includes troubleshooting, user administration, authorization profiles.
- A motivated individual and a quick learner, committed to teamwork, multicultural experience.
- Able to communicate clearly with clients and managers.

#### **SAP ECC 6.0 Experience:**

- User administration involving creation/deletion/locking/modifying users.
- Experience in Role Administration like Created and maintained Single, Derived and Composite Roles.
- Analyze and fix the missing authorizations using SU53 & ST01 and STAUTHTRACE Trace.
- Working with User Information System (SUIM).
- Good experience on AGR\* tables to get the roles data.
- Performed Transportation of newly created roles/ modified roles.
- Creating the Batch user id's for Background jobs.
- Termination of inactive users.
- Manual addition of authorization objects as per business requirement.

#### **GRC AC 12.0 EXPERIENCE:**

- Activation of BC Sets for Workflow, ARA, EAM, ARM & BRM.
- Activation of ICF services and activated the applications in clients.
- Maintaining Connectors and Connection Type.
- Create FF ID's, FF Owners, FF Controllers and FF Administrators for FF ID's and map them to FFID's.
- Adding FF ID's to Fire Fighter using EAM.
- Perform the Risk Analysis for user level and Role level in ARA.
- Maintaining Rule Set, Function ID & Risk ID with Risk Owners and generating rules.
- Creation and maintenance of Mitigation controls ID's.

# **Employment History**

- Presently working as Sap Security & GRC Consultant in Webmatics Solutions Pvt Ltd Hyderabad from July 2020 to till date.
- Worked as Civil Engineer in Srinija Drugs Pvt Ltd at Kondapalli, Vijayawada from August 2017 to June 2020.

### **Professional Summary**

### Project 2:

Company	Webmatics Solutions Pvt Ltd
Client	Honeywell
Role	SAP Security & GRC Consultant

 Client Profile: Honeywell International Inc. is an American publicly traded, multinational conglomerate corporation headquartered in Charlotte, North Carolina. It primarily operates in four areas of business: aerospace, building technologies, performance materials and technologies, and safety and productivity solutions.

#### **ROLES AND RESPONSIBILITIES:**

- User Maintenance/User creation, deletion, modification on PRD, QA & DEV Servers.
- Created and modified Single roles, Composite roles and Derived roles using profile generator (PFCG)
- Assign missing authorizations to users to perform their tasks.
- Troubleshoot security/authorization related problems using user information system (SUIM) and Display Authorization Data (SU53).
- Restricting Table Access using Authorization Objects S\_TABU\_DIS and S\_TABU\_NAM for maintaining Table Security.
- Troubleshoot authorization problems based on the user request and provided solutions.
- Comprehensive use of PFCG, SU01, SU10 and all SAP security related tables.
- Adding Authorization objects to T-codes.
- Transported Roles (Single roles/ Composite roles/ Template roles/ Child roles).
- Created FF ID's, FF Owners, FF Controllers, and FF Administrators for FF ID's and map them to FFID's.
- Adding FF ID's to Fire Fighter using EAM.
- Mitigation and Remediation of users using User Analysis in ARA.

## Project 1:

Company	Srinija Drugs Pvt Ltd
Role	Civil Engineer
ROLES AND RESPONSIBILITIES:	

- Overall project Monitoring & Closure.
- Monitoring site level activities and ensuring quality.
- Project coordination in terms of Design and site activities.
- Estimating and monitoring construction cost.
- Preparing the DPR of Projects.

### **Educational Qualifications**

- Bachelor of Engineering from SRKR Engineering College Bhimavaram, 2012-2016 with CGPA 7.94.
- Post-Graduation Programme in Quantity Surveying and Contract Management from NICMAR Hyderabad from 2016-2017 with CGPA 8.12.

#### **Extra-Curricular Activities**

- Worked as organizer for national level technical symposium SUPERNOVA 2K15 conducted by SRKR Engineering college.
- Worked as organizer for NIPUNA 2K15 conducted by SRKR Engineering College.
- Certification of participation in CIVIL SIMPLIFIED WORKSHOP (In Bridge Designing).

### **Achievements**

- Appreciation from client for completing work on time with quality.
- Secured 2<sup>nd</sup> place for paper presentation in SUPERNOVA 2K15 conducted by SRKR Engineering College.
- Selected as Executive body member of organizing committee Institute of Engineers (IE).

(TJSRVYJAYANTHI)